OUR BELOVED SUMMER
Should I begin?
MAY, 2011
Well…
Hello.
My name is Choi Ung.
CHOI UNG (19, MALE)
Let's look at the first one.
As limit x approaches one,
you can find the limiting value.
So we can think about
the case when it's smaller than one
and when it's bigger than one. Understand?
-Okay. When it's smaller than one…
-Don't look at the camera.
-But it bothers me.
-Just act like it's not here.
How can I? It's right in front of me.
For this case, it goes down like this.
-As you can see…
-So the answer is…
I'm being filmed.
You idiot. Look forward.
Should we look at the next one?
-The limiting value of this is one.
-But it's not just me.
What are you looking at?
Look at the teacher.
The limiting value of this is one as well.
The limiting values of these are the same…
This annoying brat as well.
Let's end it here.
Attention, bow.
-Thank you.
Where are you going?
It's none of your business.
Sir, can we stop for a moment?
I can't keep working with that idiot.
-"Idiot"?
-We've been filming for days.
Why can't you sit still
when we're filming?
I can't focus at all with you next to me.
How can I
when there is a camera right next to me?
Just focus on the class.
Can't you even do that?
You can ignore me
and focus on class yourself.
Can't you even do that?
I guess you don't care because
your grades couldn't get any worse.
But I won't let you bring down my grades.
You heard her, right?
Whatever. It's your social skills
that couldn't get any worse.
Why did I agree to this?
I know, right? Why did you agree to this?
My name is Kook Yeon-su.
KOOK YEON-SU (19, FEMALE)
I think I first saw Choi Ung
in tenth grade.
This much again?
I'm reading less
because I have exams soon.
You'll read all the books here
by the time you graduate.
Kook Yeon-su…
-Here. Enjoy.
-Thank you.
APRIL'S TOP BOOKWORMS
1ST: CHOI UNG
2ND: KOOK YEON-SU
-Excuse me.
-Yes?
Who is Choi Ung?
He's in first place this month, too?
Oh, Ung?
I think he was over there.
Hey.
I met him somewhere that didn't suit him.
I'm Kook Yeon-su from Class 5.
What's your rank?
-What rank?
-Your grades.
I'm 267th.
The total number of students here…
There are 267 students.
Back then, I just thought
that he was a strange kid.
No, wait. That was the second time we met.
The first time we met
was when we started high school.
The student who entered with
the highest grades is Kook Yeon-su.
Her name's Kook Yeon-su?
What a funny name.
I watched her because she walked
like she was entering a battlefield.
HWIYEONG HIGH SCHOOL ENTRANCE CEREMONY
Hey, look at her skirt.
-She's obviously a teacher's pet.
-She's a stereotype.
-They all have the same style.
-Hey, look at her shoes.
Even my mom wouldn't wear that.
-Spring is finally here.
-How tacky.
The weather is still pretty cold.
We met eyes for the first time,
so I was trying to be nice by smiling.
Hey.
What are you looking at?
But she seemed ill-tempered.
Anyway, I thought I'd never
be involved with him again.
You're here.
Did you think about that offer?
The producer's a friend of mine.
He won't trouble you too much.
You don't have to
if you think it will affect your grades.
-Will it be just me?
-No, with one more student.
It's a documentary where
they observe the best and worst students
for a month as they spend time together.
Anyway, just think about it.
Will I be paid if I agree to do it?
Of course.
He was the exact opposite of me.
Oh, you're here already.
-Hang on.
-All right.
Just a moment.
The ingredients must be here.
Check them thoroughly.
They were in a bad condition last time.
-Check them properly.
-All right.
SEAFOOD SOUP WITH UNG
POTATO SOUP WITH UNG
CHICKEN FEET WITH UNG
-Hello.
He's Ung's father.
Ung!
-Hey. Come over here.
-But things happened
regardless of my intentions.
Why didn't you tell us
about the documentary?
I said I wouldn't do it.
The producer came all the way here.
Why did you say no?
And it's with
the top student in your year.
Of course you should do it!
Of course! We don't know
what he's doing at school.
If you film that,
we'll be able to see what he does.
-That's right.
-Thank you.
-I said I'm not doing it!
Why would you refuse?
Why would I do that?
I don't want everyone to know my face.
You'll be able
to build a great memory with this.
-Right.
-I'm a senior now, you know.
Don't you think it will affect my grades?
What's he on about?
They are letting you study
with the top student in your grade.
You should be grateful!
I mean…
It was as if it had to happen.
She's kind of weird!
Anyway, that's how it all started.
Choi Ung from Class 1
will be joining us for a month.
-Yes, sir.
Be nice to him.
It may be distracting for you
since they'll be filming,
but it will be a fun experience.
And with that,
I hope you all have a great day.
-Yes, sir.
It was more bothersome than I thought.
The worst students make the most fuss.
-Are you talking to me?
-Keep your stuff off my desk.
She was way more annoying than I thought.
At first, I tried
to become friends with her.
Hey…
I'm sorry.
Can we…
I said I was sorry.
I'm not sorry.
But what can I do?
We're just so different.
No! Not here!
Darn it.
Go!
Here.
-Hey.
-Over here!
Oh, my.
Darn it. Hey!
Oh, gosh!
Are you okay?
He's so childish.
Ma'am.
How can I solve that
with the L'Hôpital's rule?
Ma'am.
Can we solve this
by using the derived function?
-Ma'am.
-Yes?
-All right, kids. Enjoy your lunch.
Ma'am.
She's so selfish.
THE UNBEARABLE LIGHTNESS OF BEING
I love lying in the shade.
The gentle breeze,
the sunlight shining through the trees…
You're so ridiculous.
Can you move?
Finish reading that
and return it to the library.
This is so nice.
He's so lazy.
Who was that?
Choi Ung! You again?
I told you to be quiet!
Things are already exhausting,
but she just makes it worse.
He's just so pathetic.
Sorry. What was the question?
Pay attention.
Oh, things I hate?
Kook Yeon-su.
I mean, I hate Kook Yeong-su.
She's some girl I know.
I hate pathetic beings.
I hate everyone who's pathetic.
Being selfish. I hate selfish people who--
People who cause trouble for others.
Why can't they just keep to themselves
and not drag others down with them?
Being harsh.
Some people talk without thinking.
They don't think at all.
Look who's talking.
He just doesn't think at all.
Wait. Are you talking about me?
You seemed to be talking about me too.
What? Are you kidding me?
No, I'm totally serious.
Why are you filming this again?
It's a show where the top student helps
the student at the bottom of the class.
-Right?
-I see.
Is this some kind of a test
to see how long you can withstand
someone who has no social skills?
Doing experiments like that
is pretty unethical.
The best student and the worst student.
Which is more anti-social?
When people like her enter society,
they will only tire out
the people around them.
Well, you wouldn't even
be able to participate in society.
How would you know?
What do you think
you'll be like in ten years?
In ten years, I'll be 29.
I'm sure I'd be good at
whatever I'm doing.
I want to live a peaceful life
without doing anything.
I'll be leading people around me,
living an active life.
A successful life.
I hope I'll live a quiet life.
-Anyway…
-One thing I know for sure is that--
…I won't have to see
this annoying face again.
That's what I wanted to say.
THE BEST AND WORST STUDENTS
SCHOOL LIFE PLAYBOOK
VIEWS
DOCUMENTARIES
LEAVING A REPLY BECAUSE NO ONE WOULD
SCHOOL LIFE PLAYBOOK
TRENDING VIDEO
SO FUNNY
AMAZING CHEMISTRY
HILARIOUS
THIS IS A MUST WATCH
PLEASE LET THERE BE A SECOND SEASON
EPISODE 1
I KNOW WHAT YOU DID LAST SUMMER
This isn't it.
THE PRESENT
Ms. Kook Yeon-su?
Yes.
I don't think you have
anything more to add. Will you continue?
This isn't the life I thought I'd live.
But still, please listen
until the end and give me your opinion.
All right, then. Continue.
I will explain
the online promotion methods.
We're planning on gaining
people's interest before the opening
through online campaigns
and participation events.
And through hashtag events--
Ms. Kook.
This is pretty disappointing.
This isn't what we asked for.
You should have
checked with us in advance.
Your ideas are too mediocre.
To attract people's interests
before the store opens,
-we should do online--
-Don't you think I know that?
-But we--
-Your company's name is Run, right?
You're a small company,
but you won quite a lot of awards,
and I heard you're
quite famous in the industry.
But your work is pathetic.
You've built up a great image
for your company, I'll give you that.
Ji-hyeon. The presentation this afternoon…
Can we reschedule it to 10 a.m.?
-Mr. Jang.
-Yes? You're done, right?
Is there anything else?
Getting looked down on like this
was never part of my plan.
-Yes. I'm not done yet.
-Hurry up, then.
Offline,
we'll be collaborating with an artist
for the opening of Soen Shop.
Isn't it cliché to use merch
to attract customers?
It isn't very effective
and is a waste of resources.
Consumers won't fall for--
Didn't you say you'd listen
until the end, Mr. Jang?
Go on.
This isn't just so that we could
lure in customers with the merchandise.
We'll be merchandising the shop itself
to promote the company.
These are the works of Ko-o,
the most popular illustrator these days.
Ko-o is known for drawing detailed
and trendy pieces based on buildings.
And recently, Ko-o received more attention
as the idol singer NJ bought one of them.
Through this collaboration,
we'll host a live drawing show
for the opening ceremony.
Go on.
The artist's image matches
the unique and innovative goods
that Soen Shop aims
to provide its customers.
Ko-o already has a large fanbase
because of his unique drawings
and his sincere attitude toward art.
If we promote the shop
with his drawing on the exterior wall,
I'm sure it will make Soen Shop
the hottest place to visit.
Can you get the artist on board?
Of course. It won't be a problem.
You'd better be right.
ARTIST KO-O
Not bad.
I don't know why you waited
until the last minute to show us that.
-The order--
-You can proceed.
Ms. Kook. That was great.
You were so cool today.
I heard Mr. Jang is very aggressive.
He sure was scary.
He's doing that on purpose.
He called us over this early
so he could have the upper hand.
He even kept cutting her off.
But still,
we have this project in the bag now.
But Ms. Kook. Can we really
get the artist to work with us?
I thought that wasn't confirmed yet.
That jerk…
When we get back to the office,
get me all the data on the artist.
Everything from his social media
to his interviews.
We have to do this project no matter what.
But the artist is known
for being a recluse.
Nobody's seen his face,
even at exhibitions.
I'm going to find him, no matter what.
How could he cut me off like that?
Did he never learn any manners?
Jeez, where is my car?
Mr. Jang.
Did you have something to say to me?
Are you opening my car door for me?
What?
I'm sorry. I haven't gotten used
to the company car yet.
I was mistaken.
-Ms. Kook.
-Yes?
I hate baseless courage.
I think irresponsible people
are the most pathetic.
-Right.
-I hope you weren't bluffing
when you said you could
get the artist on board.
You're not that pathetic, are you?
Ten years ago…
That jerk…
…I would have never imagined
that I'd be treated this way.
I had always known
that my life would be peaceful.
I've always dreamed of this.
We started a restaurant
for drivers passing by.
-Hang on.
-Why?
Wait. What's he doing?
Stop acting so weird back there.
I have to film Dad,
but you're being distracting.
You ruined the shot. It's your fault.
Stop bothering us and go inside.
But I was here first.
I thought I'd be fine talking
in front of the camera,
but it's quite nerve-racking.
-I want a little more peace though.
-Our franchise began
as a diner for drivers 25 years ago.
We specialized in
steamed fish and chicken feet.
-Then word got around--
-Stop it already!
You ruined the shot!
He's a busy man, you know.
Ung, you should go.
Aren't you late for work?
It's fine. I have time.
Then eat something before you go.
Don't you dare!
You little brat.
Stop loafing around and work on this.
Don't you think I'm busy too?
-Nonsense.
-Ridiculous.
You? Busy? You're not even working.
-Hey, put that away.
-Come on.
He's spending
his precious time helping us.
You should be thanking him.
You little brat.
Finish up and watch the counter.
And don't run away.
-Honey, help me with something.
-Wait, I…
I can't do it by myself.
Jeez. I'd better go.
I told you to stop filming.
You'd better stop if you don't
want to lose your fingers or the camera.
What happened to your face?
-Even pork is marinated for eight hours.
-What do you mean?
I only slept
two and a half hours last night.
I got less rest than pork.
That's too bad. You sleep and poop
as much as a pig though.
Shut up. And stop filming!
But I was told to film you too
for the promotional video.
No way. Don't you dare.
Ung!
-Yes?
Ung.
Over here. Look at the camera.
That's right.
How cute.
-Look over here.
-Ung! Look at Mommy.
-Ung! Over here.
-That's right.
-Look at your teacher.
-How cute!
Hang on.
Look at your teacher. Yes, good.
-Look over there.
-He grew a lot.
-It must be because your husband is tall.
-Look at your teacher.
Is he listening to his teacher?
I bought this for today.
"Choi Ung"?
Yes. I'm Choi Ung. What's your name?
I'm not going to tell you.
KIM JI-UNG
Not you. Ji-ung.
Do you want some stew?
-Yes, I'd love that.
-What about me?
You can have some too.
Hey, I've been thinking…
I'll practice my lines properly,
so would it be okay
to do this again when you have time?
Anytime is fine with me.
So call me when you want to do it.
Thank you so much.
It's so nice having a producer help out.
When else would I be able to try this?
Dad. Don't look at me like that.
The cabbages are arriving later, okay?
Don't you dare think about running away
and move them inside.
I hope you're not forgetting
that I'm your son!
-Have two bowls, alright?
-Okay.
It seems like you'll be the one
inheriting the restaurant later.
My parents are acting
like you're their son these days.
But think about it.
I act more like their son than you.
Jeez.
Aren't you working these days?
Why do you keep lurking around here
and threatening my status?
I finally got a short vacation
after finishing a program.
I'll be busy again
when I start my next project.
I should have fun here before that.
Hey! What do you think you're doing?
-I'm having fun.
-You jerk!
Wait! Father, look at Ung
holding the bean sprouts like that!
-I wasn't--
-Put that down!
Put it down.
-Put it down!
-Don't play around with that!
You're dead, you jerk!
-How can you be so childish?
-My goodness.
You're a grown-up, you know!
I thought I'd have matured
a bit more than this though.
Ms. Kook and Mr. Jang
were clashing since they're so similar.
It's so fun watching them argue.
You saw how Ms. Kook reacted
when Mr. Jang cut her off
during her presentation, right?
"Didn't you say you'd listen
until the end, Mr. Jang?" Unbelievable.
But still, Ms. Kook was so cool.
Don't you think so?
She's cool.
It wasn't something a small company
like us can easily get.
But she's getting that opportunity for us.
She's almost like
the breadwinner of this family.
Our CEO's good luck charm.
But imagine if we get on her bad side.
She's so dependable
when she's fighting our clients,
but if she ever gets angry at us…
Polar bears tear people apart
with their paws,
but Ms. Kook tears people with her words…
How did it go, Ms. Kook?
The data I asked for on Ko-o.
Have them ready by 3 p.m.
-Yes, ma'am.
-Okay.
What's going on here? What is it?
Why are you guys so good?
I heard you were given the green light.
I was so shocked.
Good work.
And I can't believe Ms. Kook
succeeded again.
Today's a day to celebrate.
-We should--
-No gatherings.
I'm not suggesting a team dinner.
Why would we do such a thing?
We shouldn't be having
a company gathering at a time like this.
We all hate it.
Then how about
-dinner--
-How about lunch instead?
You don't want to waste
your dinnertime with me?
That's not what I mean.
It's going to be hard
to get off work on time.
Then should we go have lunch now?
We already had lunch, sir.
What do you mean?
I just remembered
that we all had lunch together
on the way back.
What about me? Why didn't you invite me?
You didn't attend the presentation
because you had a stomachache.
So we thought you'd skip lunch.
Right. That was smart thinking.
Then you don't want dinner,
and you already ate lunch.
What should I do, then?
Then how about some coffee?
-Yes.
-Coffee sounds great.
-You all have coffee.
-We have coffee.
You already have coffee.
You all have some.
-Yes.
-Fine.
-Why don't I get you some porridge, then?
-Don't worry.
I hate porridge.
He seems upset.
SOL-I
SEOUL HARDWARE STORE
What is it?
You wench! Why weren't you picking up?
Why weren't you picking up?
Jeez. Don't you see that I'm working?
But still, you should answer your phone.
Darn it…
What?
What are you doing? Hey!
Get up. Exercise time.
Hey! What do you think you're doing?
Get up. You said you're not sleeping well.
Stop it! Let go of me!
It's the manager's job
to take care of the artist's health too.
I'm already exhausted,
and he makes it worse.
Aren't I a great manager? I'm so kind.
You're fired.
That counts as wrongful dismissal.
We'll stop when we
make it over there. You can do it.
I can't.
You have to go. Come on.
-Jeez.
-One, two, three, four.
Two, two, three, four.
All right! We're here!
Over here. Hurry up.
Hey! What's that?
The flag. Make the goal.
-There you go.
-Yes, goal!
You guys are doing all kinds
of stupid things.
I heard you only slept
two and a half hours.
-You have such a big mouth.
-Me? Take this.
Gosh.
Aren't you supposed to be busy?
Did you get fired?
Hey, if you're skilled,
you can slack off all you want.
Right. Did you still not
tell your parents what you do?
They just know I'm drawing.
They called me a while ago
and asked if you make enough money
since they couldn't find anything
when they searched your name.
Didn't you tell them anything?
How much do you earn? Tell me.
You're not even telling your family?
You're being overly secretive.
-Darn it.
-Jeez!
-You shook it, didn't you?
-No. So how much does he earn?
Each drawing sells for…
-What? For real?
-Yes.
Son of a bitch.
Hey. You just
wanted to swear at me, right?
Of course not.
Son of a bitch. What?
Oh, right. I told Father
that you didn't move the cabbages.
He said he'll kill you tomorrow.
-Oh, my. What are you going to do?
-Darn it.
Why is the weather so nice today?
-Jeez!
You idiots.
-You shook these, didn't you?
-Didn't you see what happened to mine?
Did I shake them? Did you?
No way.
You're ignoring me again, aren't you?
You asshole.
You really have no customers.
You might go out of business soon.
-Hey!
-Gosh, you startled me.
I can hear you
even if you whisper, you know.
Do you know how many times
you've stood that guy up?
-Three times?
-It's four.
Do you have
some kind of grudge against him?
How could I?
I've never even seen him before.
But you bailed on him when he said
he'd come to your office building?
He even went there during lunchtime
because you said you were so busy.
I totally forgot.
You're such a scumbag.
How can you be so arrogant?
How can you function as a member
of society like that?
People worse than me
are living normal lives in society.
Shut up. That guy you bailed on four times
must be totally smitten with you.
He says he really wants to meet you.
I pity him so much.
-Is that so?
-"Is that so?"
You have to see him this time.
If you bail on him again,
I'm going to cut ties with you.
All right. I'll go see him.
I'm sick of this.
I'm not telling you to date him.
Just meet some guys.
At least give it a go.
Office, home, and here.
You don't go anywhere else.
Your eyes look soulless and empty.
There's probably nothing under your skin.
Skin!
I want some pork skin. Cook me some.
My gosh. It's like talking to a wall.
Let's live soulful lives.
Is meeting guys
your idea of a soulful life?
Forget it. I'm just going to work.
-Meet someone at work then.
-That's horrible.
You're making me lose my appetite.
Then…
Could it be that
you still haven't got over--
Gosh. So this is how you
drive away your customers.
-I'm leaving.
-All right, I'll stop. I'm sorry.
Please sit down, ma'am. I'm sorry.
You have such a bad temper.
My gosh.
Let me take a break. Jeez.
Why are you so bad?
You try it then.
Goodness.
Ung. That live drawing show--
I'm not doing it.
Darn it.
Why are you so obsessed
with keeping your identity hidden?
You're living in the past.
It's all about communication these days.
He's not suited for that.
He can't even talk properly.
I really don't get it.
Five years ago, all you did was draw,
saying that you were going to succeed.
But now you're rejecting opportunities.
What are you thinking?
He's changed now that he's successful.
He's full of himself.
-Hey.
-You shouldn't be so arrogant.
I heard Nu-a is collaborating with SJ.
Who's Nu-a?
An artist who has the same style as him.
A rival of his.
"A rival"? You've got to be kidding.
Hey, Nu-a's just copying me.
At this rate, people will say
you're the one copying Nu-a.
Do you want to go back to being a bum
like five years ago?
-Why do you keep bringing up the past?
-So you'll be motivated!
Do you really want to live like that?
Jeez.
It wasn't that bad.
What are you on about?
Hey.
Let's make a bet.
If you score 15 points first,
I'll move
all the cabbages for you tomorrow.
Really?
-Come on.
-I'm game.
You won't score a single point.
Ja-gyeong!
You reek of alcohol.
Did you drink again?
I want to make a doll with your stomach.
Then I can squeeze it every day.
Get washed up and go to bed.
You have to go to work tomorrow.
Just sleep inside, even if I'm late.
Don't stay up waiting for me.
I was out here because it was hot.
Go and get washed up.
Can't you wash me?
-Wash me, Grandma.
-My goodness.
-Give me a kiss.
-What's with you?
-You've lost your mind!
-Come on.
What's gotten into you?
-Why?
-You stink! Go away.
My goodness. Unbelievable.
How much have you had to drink?
My gosh.
ARTIST KO-O
KO-O'S SOLO EXHIBITION
KO-O, THE ILLUSTRATOR
WHO PAINTS BUILDINGS WITH SOUL
WHAT EXCITES YOU THE MOST
ABOUT BUILDINGS?
YOU DRAW NATURE AS WELL AS BUILDINGS
WHAT ARE YOUR INTERESTS?
CAN YOU TELL US
ABOUT YOUR DRAWING PROCESS?
WHY AREN'T THERE PEOPLE IN YOUR DRAWINGS?
I LOVE THINGS THAT DON'T CHANGE
BUT PEOPLE CHANGE OR DISAPPEAR OVER TIME
THAT'S WHY THERE ARE NO PEOPLE
OR TIME IN MY WORKS
Ji-ung, our team leader
was looking for you.
I know. He's calling me every ten minutes.
Didn't you go home again?
Do I smell?
How many days has it been?
It's only my fourth day.
I told you to go home.
Don't make it a habit
of living in the editing room.
Mr. Park said he couldn't
go home at all when he was an assistant.
Hey, don't listen to anything he says.
There's nothing worth listening to.
-Oh, right. Chae-ran.
-Yes?
-Work with me on my next project.
-When I'm done with Mr. Park's.
It's fine. I'm going to steal you away.
Were you looking for me?
Do you know what time it is?
Let me get a proper break.
I'm guessing that you
need me to work my ass off for something.
You've gotten smart.
I'm telling you in advance.
I'm not doing documentaries
on people anymore.
Why not?
They're boring.
I want something related
to the environment. It will be perfect.
Environment? Don't you know
how tough that is?
But they're fun.
I heard Yun-jin doesn't want to do it.
Just give that to me.
Fine. Do it. I'll give you that one.
What?
What's going on?
What's gotten into you? Are you serious?
Do one on people first.
Then I'll let you do it. I swear!
Jeez. I knew it.
You'll never just let me
do something I want.
It's a simple one. It's not even a series.
Then you can get someone else to do it.
Like Mr. Han.
Hey. Look at this.
How about it?
Someone who loves me deeply,
someone I can always be with--
-Ridiculous.
-My gosh!
What? What is it?
What is it? Tell me.
How could I not know?
Why? Did you find Ko-o?
Hey, isn't that Ms. Kook?
I saw these videos before.
Why didn't I realize it was her?
Hold on. Is that the view count?
That's crazy.
Ms. Kook was harsh back then too.
She talks exactly the same way
as Mr. Jang.
Totally. She seems
harsher in these videos.
This kid's name is Ung.
She was so mean to him.
But Ung keeps fighting back.
Those two fight like cats and dogs.
But from what I remember,
Yeon-su's the one who starts the fight.
-Unbelievable.
-Is that so?
Totally.
I have the feeling that Yeon-su
has a crush on Ung.
Ms. Kook.
Hello, Ms. Kook.
Ji-un, that thing I asked for…
Ms. Kook, when…
Am I that similar to Mr. Jang?
Who? You?
Of course not.
You're much better than him.
So I'm just as annoying as he is.
-Of course not! We didn't mean that.
-No way!
I think the producers
made you look mean in the video.
Right. Did you sue them for this?
You really should.
-Right!
-Yes, you should.
What is it? Why are you all gathered here?
Is there something fun?
Do any of you know
how to get stuff like that deleted?
Well, it's from a television network,
so you should talk to them.
-Television? What's this about?
-Should I file a complaint?
Are you gathering the data?
Of course, we're getting
everything on Ko-o.
What is it? Tell me what's going on.
We have to hand over the files
by next week.
I guess you have a lot of time
on your hands.
-And Ye-in.
-Yes?
It wasn't me. It was him.
-What do you mean?
-He picked the fights first.
-Ung was always the one who started it.
-Oh, I see.
Right. What I meant was…
What is it? Tell me.
Come on. Tell me.
I won't tell anyone,
so tell me what this is about.
-No.
-Yes.
Why do you always say no?
Why would I shoot that again?
Don't you see the views?
Look at the comments.
This is the most popular documentary
on our channel.
It's just trending for a while.
Plus, it seems like
only kids are watching it.
Do you know
what our director's saying these days?
"We have to attract more young viewers."
Can you come up with a better idea
to attract young viewers than this?
Do we film anything that has
a lot of views and young viewers?
Can't you just do it?
Do you know why dating reality shows
are popular these days?
It's even more dramatic
than any of the TV series.
Look at this.
There aren't any TV series
that's this entertaining.
If we show how these kids
have changed after ten years,
it'll be epic. I guarantee you.
If we do a good job,
we'll get a totally popular documentary.
But why would I film that?
You're the one who made it.
I'm not young anymore.
I'm old now.
Plus…
SCHOOL LIFE PLAYBOOK
Hey, Ji-ung!
You must know them the best.
Do you still keep in touch with them?
How are they doing? I'm curious myself.
It's been ten years.
Have they changed a lot?
They all say he's cute.
This won't do.
"I'm an acquaintance of Choi Ung."
"He's still as weird as he is
in this video."
All right.
Ung! You have a call!
Ung!
Jeez.
Tell him I'll move the cabbages soon.
-No, it's not that.
-Do I have to do it now?
Look at it.
What's with you?
Come on. Get it. Hurry!
What?
Come on, answer it!
Hello?
It's hard to get in touch with you.
I heard you work late at night,
but you wouldn't pick up.
And I called you in the morning,
but you still didn't pick up.
Oh, NJ. I didn't know I got a call. Hello.
You must be busier than idol singers.
I guess you must be busier
since the articles got out
about me buying your drawing.
Right. More people seem to
want to buy my drawings now. Thank you.
Is that it, though?
I want to see more of your work.
-What are you doing today?
-Oh, I'm moving cabbages--
What?
Jeez!
I'm actually moving cabbages--
Do you want to meet up later today?
I want to take a look around your studio.
Oh, today?
Yes, today. I think I can end early.
I see.
Tell her to come.
All right. Then let me know
when you're getting off work.
-Okay. I'll call you later then.
-Okay.
Oh, my god! This is crazy!
-Were you staying in touch with NJ?
-This is the first time.
When did you exchange numbers?
She asked for my number first.
She asked for your number? Why?
I don't know. Get away from me.
You're scaring me.
This is awesome! I can't believe it!
This must be a dream.
Choi Ung had a phone call with NJ.
-This is insane.
-But…
She called because she wants
a free drawing, right?
What?
I mean…
-"Is that it?" And then she said…
-Is that it?
-I want to see more of your work.
-"I want to see more of your work."
She wants a drawing for free, right?
Ung. NJ just bought a building
worth 15 billion won last week.
And just give her one if she asks.
Give her anything she wants.
Just give her everything you have!
Give her everything!
Is NJ really coming here?
I can't believe it!
-What should I wear?
-Hey, let me see your hands.
What for?
If you go through my stuff again,
you're dead.
I might die before that.
My heart's about to burst.
I've been a fan since her trainee days.
So let me off this time.
Do you think it makes sense
for you to be wearing that at home?
I guess you're right.
-Darn it. What do I wear?
-Jeez.
There's nothing to wear.
What?
Why are there two of these?
-Hey, that's--
-It's tacky.
No way.
Is that a matching couple's shirt?
What with the long face?
Shut up.
You wore matching t-shirts?
How cute.
A leather jacket.
Would it be too much?
Hello. Are you with someone?
Yes.
Mr. Jang?
This is pretty awkward.
What are you doing here alone?
Well, what does it look like?
Your reservation table is this way.
Oh, all right.
Ms. Kook Yeon-su?
You're Choi Ung, right?
You were in that documentary.
The worst student.
-No, I'm not.
-Come on. You are!
Hey, he said it's not him. Let's go.
I'm sure it's him!
He looks exactly the same.
Mr. Kang Min-su?
Yes. Please sit.
You finally came.
I'm sorry about last time.
-It's fine.
-Well, then shall we…
I still wanted to see you
even after being stood up four times
because I wanted to check something.
-What--
-We first set a date
to meet in Yeoido at 7 p.m.,
but you didn't come.
And then we set a date
to meet at Hongdae at eight.
You stood me up both times
because of work.
Well, I--
The third was on a weekend.
We were to meet at three,
but you called at five-to
and canceled because of work.
The fourth was the lunch yesterday.
We were supposed to meet for 30 minutes
during lunch at your company building,
but you forgot that due to work.
I guess you're doing all the work
at your company.
Mr. Kang…
So I told your friend for the fifth time
that I wanted to see you.
I just couldn't give up like that.
I was worried
that you wouldn't turn up again.
But thank you for coming.
I'm sorry about last time.
I was wondering
if you were worth
all the time I was wasting,
but I see that you're not.
-What?
-This might seem petty…
That's right.
This is why I wanted to see you.
I hope you meet a nice man.
Wait…
I'm not sure you'll be able to though.
Bye, then.
Did you hear everything?
No.
You say that, but that smile
on your face bothers me.
I could hear everything.
I'd appreciate it
if you could pretend you didn't.
Do you mean about the blind date itself,
or about how you were rejected?
Which do you mean?
Your food is ready, sir.
Thank you.
Enjoy.
Seems like you're eating alone.
Mind if I join you?
Wouldn't it be awkward
since we're wearing the same shirt?
I think it'll be weirder to eat separately
with the same shirt on.
I'll pay for my own food,
so just let me sit here.
Fine, then.
Stupid rain… My shoot isn't ending.
I'm so sorry.
Could I head over tomorrow morning?
Are you going to keep being such a bore?
I never considered myself boring.
Do you drink alone like this often?
Sometimes, after work.
I see. I guess you
must be an empty shell too.
I don't understand.
My teammates say that you and I are alike.
I'm not sure. Only our shirts are alike.
I was kind of startled when I heard that.
As I was looking at you,
I told myself that
I was much more human than you.
Are you drunk?
Or are you pretending to be?
I don't get drunk.
The amount of liquor I can hold
has increased over time.
There really isn't anything to talk about.
I can talk endlessly about work,
but I don't want to right now.
I'm ready to hear anything work-related.
Well, what should I talk about?
That shirt.
How much was it?
I used a discount coupon
and got it really cheap.
I'd be upset if I paid more for it.
I paid full price for it.
That's good to hear.
But isn't it kind of amazing?
Wearing the same shirt
and coming to the same place.
It's my first time wearing
the same clothes as someone else.
This is still quite awkward.
You never wore matching t-shirts?
I hate pathetic stuff like that.
I used to hate pathetic things too.
But I guess you've
done it before.
Well, you know…
Sometimes you become someone else.
-Is that so?
-I knew it.
I really am more human than you.
That again?
I used to be so childish.
Can I have a glass of that wine too?
Wine and soju aren't a great match.
It's fine. I enjoy all kinds of alcohol.
Darn it.
Gosh, Eun-ho.
Jeez.
So…
just like ten years ago…
Eun-ho!
Darn it!
Jeez!
What time is it?
Hey, Eun-ho!
Aren't you going to get the door?
…it all happened
regardless of my intentions again.
Who…
As if it had to happen.
I thought I'd never
be involved with him again.
It's better to just give up.
Why? Are they still on bad terms?
Do they still fight all the time?
The thing about love and hate is that
there is a very thin line between them.
They're two sides of the same coin.
What are you on about?
They were together
for about five years.
They actually dated?
Darn it!
-Will you close the door again?
-And they broke up pretty badly.
They hurt each other so much
that they'll probably never
see each other again.
I KNOW WHAT YOU DID LAST SUMMER
-What did you say?
-Let's break up.
Do you really have to do this now?
Why shouldn't I?
This is the fifth time.
Two of them were you.
-Do you really mean it? Gosh.
-Yes.
You're at it again.
You just need everything to go your way.
What? What is it this time?
You always make conclusions
by yourself without talking to me.
You always thought that
about me, didn't you?
-I'm the selfish bitch, aren't I?
-Stop that.
You just don't want to be
the one to break up.
-Yeon-su.
-I'll be a bitch, just like you wanted.
So let's end this, okay?
Yeon-su!
I bought you that shirt.
OUR BELOVED SUMMER
I wouldn't have come to see you
if it wasn't for this.
Is that so?
-What?
-So how was it to see her again?
-I don't even remember what I said.
-Are you nuts?
-Do you like me that much or not?
-Hey, don't.
Stop following me.
I think someone is
stealing your car right now.
They look like a couple
that they're together.
You bastard.
It's been five years after all.
What if I was serious
and didn't act childish?
Would you have managed?
Subtitle translation by: Ju-young Park
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs